# **MOHAMED BRZAN**

# Frontend Developer

\$\ +201113772369 @ mohamedmahmoudbrzan@gmail.com

#### SUMMARY

Passionate Frontend Engineer with 2+ years of experience in developing web applications and. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies. Able to work independently of remote locations or in office environments as needed by the company.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

11/2022 - 2022

Mostagl

Egypt, Tanta

Successfully Built the entire website.

Used Redux/toolkit to handle the state.

- Used Bootstrap to make the website responsive on all devices.
- Used React.js to make single page application.

Web Developer

08/2022 - 10/2022

Mostagl

Egypt, Tanta

· Successfully Built the entire website.

- Used Redux/toolkit to handle the state.
- Used Bootstrap to make the website responsive on all devices.
- Used React.js to make single page application.

#### Frontend Developer

08/2021

Mostagl

Egypt, Tanta

- · Successfully Built the website interface.
- Used Bootstrap to make responsive website.
- Used React.js to make single page application.

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Arts, Surveyor Engineering

08/2014 - 08/2019

**Tanta University** 

Egypt

#### **LANGUAGES**

**Arabic** 

Native

English

Intermediate



# FIND ME ONLINE



#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/moha med-brzan-01966518a/



# YouTube

ttps://www.youtube.com/channel/U Cg0mT9zI0kJFgZGRWOajKaQ



#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

# Finished Military service in Egypt

I learned in the Army discipline and consistency moreover continuity

# Join department of surveyor in faculty of arts

by studying smart I join the department of surveyor.

#### **SKILLS**

#### Tools

HTML5 · CSS · CSS3 · Bootstrap . Sass ·

Javascript . OOP . React.js · OOP ·

Material UI · Redux/toolkit · Git · NPM

#### **Operating Systems**

Windows

#### **STRENGTHS**



# ★ Typing Fast

I'm typing 55 word per minute with small and capital characters moreover symbol characters.

# Team Leader

I have a team now with 10 members most of them work with wordpress and wocommerce.